{
    "subject": "resource/SiteGround",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "SiteGround",
    "human_readable": "The name of SiteGround is SiteGround.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9605967402458191,
            "question": "What is the name of SiteGround?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9213836789131165,
            "question": "Does SiteGround have a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8977981209754944,
            "question": "Where is SiteGround located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7998018860816956,
            "question": "Is SiteGround a company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7721179127693176,
            "question": "Who are the customers of SiteGround?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7317681908607483,
            "question": "How popular is SiteGround?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6832109689712524,
            "question": "When was SiteGround founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6742390990257263,
            "question": "What services does SiteGround provide?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6406997442245483,
            "question": "What are SiteGround's values?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5276646614074707,
            "question": "Does SiteGround have any partnerships?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of SiteGround is SiteGround.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4812_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are SiteGround's values?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4812_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What services does SiteGround provide?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4812_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was SiteGround founded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4812_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_167.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4812_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly refer to a company called \"SiteGround\" multiple times, thus supporting the triple that the name of SiteGround is indeed SiteGround."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}